{
    "subject": "resource/The_Adventures_of_Rocky_and_Bullwinkle",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:2000s_comedy_films",
    "human_readable": "The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle is a subject of the category 2000s comedy films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9606761932373047,
            "question": "What makes 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle' a representative film of the 2000s comedy genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9478826522827148,
            "question": "Is 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle' considered a comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7402685880661011,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6590491533279419,
            "question": "Who are some other prominent filmmakers associated with the 2000s comedy genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565675139427185,
            "question": "Name a popular movie from the 2000s comedy genre."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6026933193206787,
            "question": "What other films are similar to 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle' in genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5978335738182068,
            "question": "How did 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle' influence subsequent comedies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5883489847183228,
            "question": "What were some popular trends in comedy during the 2000s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5851185917854309,
            "question": "What are some critical reviews of 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41101568937301636,
            "question": "In what decade was 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle is a subject of the category 2000s comedy films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6270_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some critical reviews of 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6270_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some popular trends in comedy during the 2000s?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6270_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle' influence subsequent comedies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6270_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6270_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple \"The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle is a subject of the category 2000s comedy films\" by mentioning various details about the film, such as its release year (2000), genre (comedy), and production company (Universal Pictures)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that \"The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle\" is a 2000 film, which falls under the category of the 2000s. Additionally, it's described as an \"animated/live-action buddy comedy-drama adventure film,\" supporting its classification as a comedy film from the 2000s."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}